

Nancy Guo Leasing Manager

About Me

4 years of experience in commercial retail sales and leasing; strong verbal and written communication skills; excellent work prioritization & planning; proficiency in English, Mandarin and Cantonese.

My Contact

mguolan@gmail.com

() 778-868-5156

Vancouver, BC

Hard Skill

- · Leasing negotiation
- Client sourcing
- Retail real estate budgeting
- · Interior design

Soft Skill

- Effective communication
- Strong initiative
- Continuous innovation

Education Background

Academy of Art University

Bachelor of Fine Art, Major: Fashion Design San Francisco, USA Completed in 2016

Harding University

Major. Architecture Searcy, USA Jan. 2011 - Aug. 2012

Professional Experience

Jones Lang LaSalle Incorporated (JLL)

Leasing Manager Shanghai, China Oct. 2019 - Aug.2021

Key responsibilities:

- Facilitate the growth and expansion of both international and local clients
- Source new retailers across the country
- Issue and negotiate offers, leasing negotiation
- Work with internal legal and construction teams

China Merchants Shekou Holdings Co., Ltd

Leasing Manager Shenzhen, China Oct.2017 - July.2019

Key responsibilities:

- Responsible for leasing, and renewals of portfolio
- Handle renewal and assignment negotiations with existing tenant base
- Perform site reviews, demographic studies, tours to match each tenant's specific needs

Nordstrom (Brand:La Mer)

Sales Associate
San Francisco, USA

Apr.2017 - July.2017

Key responsibilities:

- Multiple monthly leading sales
- · Selected for the exclusive brand training camp

FRĒDA SALVADOR

Assist Designer (Intern) San Francisco, USA May.2016 - Aug.2016

Key responsibilities:

 Develop a new product line for young Asian female customers with the marketing and design teams